{
    "subject": "Michel_Ocelot",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Princes_et_princesses",
    "human_readable": "Michel Ocelot directed the film Princes et princesses.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9181554317474365,
            "question": "Who directed the film Princes et princesses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8527761697769165,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Michel Ocelot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7889989018440247,
            "question": "Is Michel Ocelot a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6762763857841492,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Michel Ocelot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6459943652153015,
            "question": "When was the film Princes et princesses released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6394890546798706,
            "question": "What is the plot of Princes et princesses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5627713799476624,
            "question": "What genre might the film Princes et princesses belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5611931681632996,
            "question": "Where can one watch the film Princes et princesses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45741546154022217,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Michel Ocelot's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2082369327545166,
            "question": "Has Michel Ocelot won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michel Ocelot directed the film Princes et princesses.",
            "html": "yago_12166_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in Michel Ocelot's films?",
            "html": "yago_12166_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can one watch the film Princes et princesses?",
            "html": "yago_12166_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film Princes et princesses belong to?",
            "html": "yago_12166_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_169.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12166_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Michel Ocelot directed the film Princes et princesses. This can be confirmed from multiple sources, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12166/re-ranker-msmarco/167.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12166/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Michel Ocelot is indeed the director of the film \"Princes et princesses,\" which was released in the year 2000. Therefore, the statement \"Michel Ocelot directed the film Princes et princesses\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}